[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Over 600 Clydesdale horses are registered every year in the United States.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Evil Dead was released in 1985 and cost $150,000 to make.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of substance does the female redeye cicada prefer for laying eggs into?", "correct_answer": "Plant tissue", "incorrect_answers": ["Dead animal matter", "Animal and human hair", "Living animal organisms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After 10 years of research LOreal found this molecule, which effectively stops hair loss.", "correct_answer": "Aminexil", "incorrect_answers": ["Ceramide", "THC", "Nanozome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Keanu Reeves starred in the 2005 movie Thumbsucker.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Inert gases are found in Group 18 of the Periodic Table. Which is the inert gas with atomic number 54?", "correct_answer": "Xe", "incorrect_answers": ["Rn", "Kr", "Ar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of bread is the Turkish bread variety called Yufka?", "correct_answer": "Flatbread", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Very long bread", "Spherical bread"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What classic song is often played at weddings during the brides dance with her father?", "correct_answer": "Daddys Little Girl", "incorrect_answers": ["White Wedding", "Poppa Dont Preach", "Now and Forever"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can tigers live to be 20 years old?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Eve of Destruction, after Eve broadsides the road rage driver on the winding road in northern California, what word comes across her creators beeper?", "correct_answer": "armed", "incorrect_answers": ["forgive", "sorry", "next?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At what New York nightclub did American socialite Little Edie have a cabaret act for about two weeks?", "correct_answer": "Reno Sweeny", "incorrect_answers": ["Irma Le Deuce", "The Gay Parie", "Les Follies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is the crest of the American Falls if measured along the jagged lip of the falls?", "correct_answer": "950  feet  (290 m)", "incorrect_answers": ["393  feet  (120 m)", "688  feet  (210 m)", "1310 feet  (400 m)"]}]